allenpress.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy Allen Press

At Allen Press, we value the privacy of our customers and everyone who accesses our online services. The Privacy Policy provided below describes how your personal data is collected and used.

Information You Provide  
Allen Press collects information provided voluntarily by users on its website. For example, Allen Press collects user-submitted data related to filling out the ‘Contact Us’ form, applying for a job, requesting a quote, or subscribing to its blog. The information Allen Press collects at these points is directly related to the communication, product, or service the user is requesting or accessing. It includes basic information that may identify the user, such as name, address, telephone number, email address, or other details. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time. 

Allen Press also handles data for its customers in accordance with their request for or use of its services. Allen Press’s customers remain the data controllers of any data they provide to Allen Press that is related to the execution of its services. Allen Press acts in accordance with the instructions of its customers regarding the collection, storage, processing, retrieval, deletion, and/or transfer of customer data. 

Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically  
In addition to user-submitted information, we may automatically collect basic information that is not personally identifiable to an individual user, such as IP address, internet service provider, the browser used to visit the website, and other anonymous website usage data. 

Allen Press uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Allen Press website, and their website access preferences. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. In addition, Allen Press uses cookies to improve user experiences on the Allen Press website. If you wish to do so, you can set your web browser to block all cookies, including those collected by Allen Press, or to prompt you when a cookie is being sent. 

Additionally, Allen Press uses Google Analytics to identify and analyze trends in the usage of its website. Any reports created with this data will be for internal use only. You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking by using the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. 

Contact your Sales Executive, Account Manager, or info@allenpress.com if you have any concerns or would like more information about our data collection practices. 

Usage and Sharing  
Allen Press collects data for the express purpose of providing its services to our clients. As such, we will not sell, share, or rent information collected on our website or blog to third parties, except as described in this statement. We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information to third parties for their promotional use.  
We use both personal and non-personal data for internal purposes, including enriching your experience with our online services, gathering information about demographics and usage patterns, and enabling purchases of goods and services. We may disclose your personal information when we believe we have a legal obligation to do so. 

Links to Third-Party Websites  
Sometimes we work with third-parties on your behalf, and we also provide links to industry-related organizations you might find helpful. These third-party websites are outside of the control of Allen Press. When you access these sites, their policies will govern your activity, and we encourage you to review them. 

Data Breach  
In the event of a data breach, our policy is to notify everyone whose data was involved in the breach. If you have questions about a reported breach, please contact your Sales Executive, Account Manager, or our Privacy Officer at privacy.officer@allenpress.com. 

Notification of Changes to Allen Press’s Privacy Policy  
Our privacy policy was last updated on May 21, 2018. Allen Press will post any changes to this policy on this public website.
